(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
せーの！
One, two!
こんこよー！博衣こよりです！
Konkoyo! I'm Hakui Koyori!
はい！ハッシュタグ博衣こより3Dよろしくお願いします！
Yes! Please use the hashtag Hakui Koyori 3D!
オッケー！こよは頭脳！頭脳派ですから！
Okay! Koyo is a brain! I'm the intellectual type!
はい、やったー！こよりスケッチ！
Yes, did it! Koyori Sketch!
いぇーい、はい！せーの！
Yay, yes! One, two!
はい！はい！はい！はい！研究室らしー全開！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Lab-style at full throttle!
はい！はい！はい！はい！全開！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Full throttle!
はい！はい！はい！はい！こよりの助手くん、わんわんわん！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Koyori's assistants, bow-wow-wow!
はい！はい！はい！はい！ケモ耳！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Animal ears!
はい！はい！はい！はい！しっぽぴこぴこ！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Tail twitching!
はい！はい！はい！はい！頭脳派なんで！見守って！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! I'm the brainy type! Watch over me!
はい！はい！はい！はい！可愛いですよ！いぇーい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! I'm cute! Yay!
はい！はい！はい！はい！オッケー！博衣こよりです！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes! Okay! I'm Hakui Koyori!
やったー！間に合ったー！
Did it! I made it!
マヨネーズは飲み物です！ちなみに、うどん好きです！
Mayonnaise is a drink! By the way, I love udon!
はい！全開！
Yes! Full throttle!
みんなー！今日は、待ちに待った
Everyone! Thank you for coming to my
こよりの3Dお披露目配信に来てくれてありがとう！
long-awaited 3D debut stream today!
初見さんも関係なく楽しめるように
I'll do my best so that even
頑張っていくので、最後まで楽しんでってね！
first-timers can enjoy it, so please have fun!
満点な人生も
A perfect life,
秀才な解答もございません
Nor a brilliant answer, I have none.
有害な評論も
Harmful reviews,
見え透いた同情も聞きたくはないな
Nor transparent sympathy, I don't want to hear.
壮観な表彰も
A spectacular award ceremony,
平凡な真っ当もございません
Nor an ordinary decency, I have none.
暗澹な将来も
A gloomy future,
傲慢な快晴も見たくはないな
Nor an arrogant clear sky, I don't want to see.
はいはい　俯いちゃって　ヤンヤンヤン　フラフラリ
Yes, yes, head down, yan yan yan, swaying about.
彷徨って
Wandering around.
正答　失っちゃって　わーんわーんわん　だって！
Losing the answer, wah, wah, wah, because!
心は満たされない！
My heart cannot be satisfied!
愛を頂戴　感情烈火メッタッタッタ　声枯らせ
Give me love, a conflagration of emotions, scream it out.
全然わかんない
I don't understand it at all.
罰点喰らい尽くせ　心臓血漿ダッタッタッタ　踊り舞え
Devour the failing marks, heart plasma, dance away.
正解なんてバイバイ推奨
I recommend saying goodbye to correct answers.
だっだっだっだわーお！
Da da da da, wow!
満点な答案も
A perfect answer sheet,
優秀な成功もございません
Nor a superior success, I have none.
後悔な人生も
A life of regret,
停滞の殺到も見たくはないな
Nor a rush of stagnation, I don't want to see.
毎回　躓いちゃって　キャンキャンキャン　フラフラリ
Stumbling every time, kyan kyan kyan, swaying about.
孕んで
Being filled with it.
正答　無くなっちゃって　わーんわーんわん　待って！
Losing the answer, wah, wah, wah, wait!
出口も見当たらない？
I can't even find the exit?
愛を頂戴　感情熱唱メッタッタッタ　声枯らせ
Give me love, singing with emotion, scream it out.
燦然止まんない
This brilliance won't stop.
罰点笑い倒せ　心臓真っ赤カッタッタッタ　踊り舞え
Laugh off the failing marks, heart red, dance away.
正解なんて無い無い提唱
I advocate that there are no correct answers.
だっだっだっだわーお！
Da da da da, wow!
愛を頂戴　感情裂傷メッタッタッタ　歌唄え
Give me love, a laceration of emotions, sing a song.
全然染まんない
I won't be tainted at all.
喝采撃ち通せ　心境烈火カッタッタッタ　這い上がれ
Shoot through the applause, a fiery mind, crawl up.
正解なんて曖昧実証
A vague demonstration of what is correct.
愛を頂戴　感情烈火メッタッタッタ　声枯らせ
Give me love, a conflagration of emotions, scream it out.
全然わかんない
I don't understand it at all.
罰点喰らい尽くせ　心臓血漿ダッタッタッタ　踊り舞え
Devour the failing marks, heart plasma, dance away.
正解なんてバイバイ推奨
I recommend saying goodbye to correct answers.
正解なんて無い無い提唱
I advocate that there are no correct answers.
だっだっだっだわーお！
Da da da da, wow!
はーい！みんなー！
Hi! Everyone!
こんこよー！見えてますかー！
Konkoyo! Can you see me?
ホロライブ6期生、秘密結社holoXの頭脳、
I'm Hakui Koyori, the brain of Secret Society holoX,
博衣こよりだよー！
Hololive 6th Gen!
ということで、博衣こよりの3Dお披露目配信、はじまるよー！
And so, Hakui Koyori's 3D debut stream is starting!
皆さーん！
Everyone!
最初に、まずはデビューの時に出した歌ってみたの曲、Lumaを歌って踊ってみたのですが、どうだったかなー？
First, I sang and danced to "Luma," the cover song I released at my debut. How was it?
なんとですね、こちら、サビは先生に振り付けしていただいたんですけど...
And you know, the chorus was choreographed by a teacher...
サビ以外はですね、こよりが考えたダンスになってまーす！
But for the rest of it, the dance was created by Koyori!
よかったら後でそんなことも考えながら、またもう一回見てみてください。
I hope you'll watch it again later with that in mind.
イエーイ！うおー！動いてるよ、みんな！助手くん！イエーイ、イエーイ、イエーイ！
Yay! Whoa! It's moving, everyone! Joshikun! Yay, yay, yay!
と、いうことで、あっ、待って。息が切れちゃったんで、あの水、飲んできていいですか？ちょっと水取ってくるね。
And so... Wait. I'm out of breath, so can I drink some water? I'll go get some water.
ふー、はー。これはもう水分補給しないとやってられないよね、って。
Phew. I really need to hydrate, don't I?
ぷはー！うめー！今日も水がうめー！
Phew! Delicious! The water is great today too!
あっ、助手くんも？助手くんも飲みたい？飲みたい？
Oh, Joshikun too? Joshikun, do you want to drink too? You do?
せーの！
Ready, go!
はい、こよりの大好きなマヨネーズ、作ってもらいました。
Yes, I had them make my favorite mayonnaise for me.
あー、よお飲める、よお飲める。はー！よし、これでもうバッチリです。
Ah, I can really drink this. Ha! Alright, now everything's perfect.
もうね、疲れも万全に取れたので、ちょっとこの「こよりずラボ」見てもらおうと思いまーす。
I'm fully refreshed now, so I'd like to show you my "Koyolabo."
あ、その前にですね、大事なこと。
Oh, before that, something important.
今日のこの3Dライブ、ぜひこのハッシュタグ「#博衣こより3D」をつけて、いっぱいスクショ撮って拡散してくださいね！ツイッターでツイートよろしくよろしくお願いしまーす！
For today's 3D live, please take lots of screenshots and spread them with the hashtag #HakuiKoyori3D! Please tweet about it on Twitter!
それでは、じゃあちょっと、まず、そうだ！みんな、ちょっと心の事、気になってるんじゃないかな？こよと一緒に、見て！心もウィインウィイン、一緒に3Dになったんですよ！ロボこよて、心ですね。
Now then, let's... oh, right! Everyone, I bet you're curious about Kokoro! Look, Kokoro is here with me in 3D too! This is Robo-Koyote Kokoro.
このロボこよて、持つことができるので、ちょっとここから出よっか、ねえ？ずっと入ってるのもね、嫌だもんね。よし、ここから出しちゃうよ。
Since I can hold this Robo-Koyote, let's have her come out, okay? It's no fun being inside all the time. Alright, coming out now!
よいしょ！心だよー。
Up we go! It's Kokoro!
「ボク、ココロ。みんな、よろしくね。ロボこよて、ノ、ココロ、ダヨ！」
I'm Kokoro. Nice to meet everyone. I'm the Robo-Koyote Kokoro!
ほら、ちゃんとこよのポッケから出てるんですよ。いいー！可愛いでしょう？イエーイ、イエーイ、心も。
See, she comes right out of Koyori's pocket! Nice! Isn't she cute? Yay, yay, Kokoro too.
なんかちょっと、さっきよりデカくなったような気が...うん、まあ、ごほんごほん、しますが。それは置いといて、心もこんな風になってるんですが。
I feel like she's gotten a bit bigger than before... well, *cough cough*. Anyway, Kokoro is like this now.
あの、助手くんたちの姿もね、この心と同じロボこよてなんですよね。で、ちょっと見分けがつかないなってことで。
And you know, the Joshikun are also Robo-Koyotes just like Kokoro. So it's hard to tell them apart.
今回、新たなデザインをですね、作っちゃったんですよ。じゃあちょっと心戻ってもらって。よいしょ。
So this time, I've created a new design! Alright, Kokoro, time to go back. Up we go.
ではでは、そんな助手くんを今から大量生産していきたいと思います。みんながいっぱい応援してくれているコメントやスーパーチャットの力をエネルギーにして、なんとこのラボ、動くんです！ちょっと動かしてみようかな？
Now then, I'm going to start mass-producing those Joshikun. Using the energy from all your supportive comments and Super Chats, this lab actually moves! Should I try moving it?
それでは...動け、こよラボ！
Alright... Move, Koyolabo!
動いたー！見て、あ、もう、ゲーミング助手くんが生まれちゃった！
It moved! Look, oh, a gaming Joshikun was already born!
見てください、このように。えー、助手くんがですね、スーパーチャットの、あの、原理で、何？スーパーチャットの力を得て大量生産されていくようになりました！可愛い！
Look at this! The Joshikun are now being mass-produced by the... principle of Super Chats? By obtaining the power of Super Chats! So cute!
しかもね、この首輪がついてるのが助手くんのデザインという風に、ね、新しくなりましたので。みんな、首輪をプレゼントだよ。イエーイ！
And also, the design for Joshikun has been updated with these collars. Everyone, here's a collar for you! Yay!
あとですね、さらにこのラボ、花火まで出すことができます！これ！これもみんなの応援のおかげで、パハーンパハーン出てますので。ありがとう！
Also, this lab can even set off fireworks! Look! These are going off thanks to everyone's support. Thank you!
あ、しかも今この花火は多分ですね、なんとツイッターのトレンド1位になったということで、みんな、いっぱいツイートもありがとう！お祝いの花火じゃ！こよやー！
Oh, and these fireworks are probably because we hit #1 on Twitter trends! Everyone, thank you so much for all the tweets! Celebratory fireworks! Koyoya!
あ、出なかった。あ、出た出た。こよやーって言った時出んのかいってなったわ。
Oh, they didn't come out. Oh, there they go. I was like, "They don't come out when I say Koyoya?"
ってわけで、まあまだまだちょっと見せたいところいっぱいあるんですが。今日はですね、みんなに楽しんでいただけるようにコーナーを準備しているんで、まずは一つ目のコーナーに行っちゃおうと思いまーす。
And so, while there's still so much more I want to show you... I've prepared some corners for everyone to enjoy today, so let's move on to the first one!
一つ目のコーナーは、こちら！「ゲストからの指令に答えろ！」イエーイ！
The first corner is this! "Answer the instructions from the guest!" Yay!
ゲストからの指令に答えろ！
Answer the instructions from the guest!
ということで、こよりは研究者なので、ゲストから色んな指令に答えて色んなポーズ...
So, since Koyori is a researcher, I'll answer various instructions from the guest and do different poses...
...することができる
...be able to do.
...できれば
...if I can,
なんかすごいスクショが
I can get some amazing screenshots,
生むこと...
creating...
スクショを生むことができるのではなかろうかという
I thought I might be able to create some great screenshots,
検証を行っていこうと思います
so I'm going to conduct a verification project.
え、そしてですね、この検証に成功すると
And if this verification is successful,
なんと、この「こよラボ」の、とある
I'll be able to unveil a certain function
機能をお披露目することができるらしいですよ
of this "Koyo Lab"!
んー、気になるよね！
Hmm, intriguing, right?
では、さっそく、ゲストをお呼びしちゃおうと思います
Now, let's call our guests right away!
まずは...
First up...
ホロックスのみんなー！
Everyone from HoloX!
聞こえるかな？
Can you hear them?
あーー！いぇー！
Aaaah! Yay!
いぇー！みんな見てるー！
Yay! We're watching!
こよちゃーーん！
Koyo-chaaan!
いぇーー！
Yaaay!
テンション高い！
You're so hyped!
わー！ありがとう！
Wow! Thank you!
めっちゃかわいい！
You're so cute!
でしょでしょ？
Right, right?
最高！最高！
The best! The best!
すごい！花火もバンバン打ちてー！
Awesome! I wanna set off fireworks too!
ねー！いいよ花火！
Yeah! Fireworks are great!
一緒に踊りたそうに、歌おうに！
Let's sing and dance together!
それではラプちゃんから、あの、名前の自己紹介お願いします
Now, La+-chan, please introduce yourself.
刮目せよ！吾輩だ。ラプラス・ダークネスです！えい！
Behold! It is I. I'm La+ Darknesss! Ei!
はーい！待ったかね？鷹嶺ルイです！えい！
Hi! Did you wait? I'm Takane Lui! Ei!
はいさー！沙花叉クロヱです！えだー！
Haisa! I'm Sakamata Chloe! Eda!
はい！風真いろはでござる！ござるー！
Hi! I'm Kazama Iroha de-gozaru! Gozaru!
てことでホロックスの４人に来てもらいましたー！
So, we have the four members of HoloX here!
わーい！にゃーい！いぇーい！
Yay! Nya-i! Yay!
なんかしてほしいポーズある？
Is there any pose you want me to do?
はいはいはいはい！
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
吾輩が大好きなやつ、やってもらっていいですか？
Can you do the one I love?
なになに？
What is it?
はい、はい、はい、やったー！間に合ったー！のポーズやってほしいな！
I want you to do the "Yes, yes, yes, YAY! I made it!" pose!
オッケーオッケー、じゃああれにフリをつけるから、オープニングに！
OK, I'll add a move to it, like an intro!
そうそうそうそう、やってほしい！
Yes, yes, yes, please do it!
はい、はい、はい、はい、やったー！間に合ったー！
Yes, yes, yes, yes, YAY! I made it!
わー！かわいいー！
Wow! So cute!
めちゃかわいい！
Super cute!
本物！本物！
The real deal! The real deal!
これ見に来たまであるぞ！
I'm basically here just to see this!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
私もちょっと気になってるところがあるんだけど...
There's something I'm curious about too...
なになになに？
What is it?
なんか、なんかチャームポイントがあるとかないとか...
I heard there's a certain charm point...
そう、あるんだけど
Yes, there is.
チャームポイントどこだ？
Where is the charm point?
え、ルイ姉さすがだね。ちょっと今まで見せられなかったチャームポイントなんだけど
Lui-nee, good catch. It's a charm point I haven't shown before.
これ見て！
Look at this!
うわーー！穴ー！
Whoa! A hole!
えろ！
Risqué!
そこじゃなくて
Not that part.
もっと見せろよ！
Show us more!
穴がね、あな...
The hole, the ho...
穴とかいいんですか、映しちゃって
Is it okay to show the hole on screen?
それは受け取り手の問題だからな！
It's all in the eye of the beholder!
いやめっちゃえち！最高！
No, that's super sexy! The best!
いいよ、しっぽも出てるよ、かわいい！
It's great, the tail is out too, cute!
かわいい！めちゃくちゃいい！もふもふ！
So cute! It's so good! Fluffy!
うわー恥ずかしい！ちょっとちょっと
Wow, I'm blushing! Hold on, hold on.
沙花叉、やってほしいなー、あるんだよね！
Sakamata has one I want you to do too!
オッケーオッケーなになに？
OK, OK, what is it?
まず手を後ろに組みます
First, put your hands behind your back.
はい
OK.
はい、座ります
Now, sit down.
はい、細かいな
OK, so detailed.
座る、はい
Sitting, OK.
なんか嫌な予感するぞ、なんでだろう
I have a bad feeling about this, I wonder why.
えー、顔を困らせて
Um, make a troubled face.
困らせる...え？なになにこれ？
Troubled face... Eh? What's this?
はい、はい、出来上がり！はいこれ、誘拐されてます、助けてください！
Yes, yes, it's done! Look, you've been kidnapped, please save me!
お前の趣味だろ！やめろ！
That's just your fetish! Stop it!
閉めときます、すいません！
I'll lock her up, sorry!
エロライバーするな！ほら！
Don't be an "Eroliver"! Come on!
どういうことだか！
What was that about?!
ロープとかないわけ？
Wait, no ropes?
ないわよ！
Of course not!
ないわよじゃないわ！
Don't "of course not" me!
さすが玄人なんだね
As expected of a pro.
で、いろはちゃんなんかある？
And Iroha-chan, do you have one?
風真はやっぱこよちゃんのね、ぴこーんってなる耳見たいから、目パキラーってなったりしないかなー
I really want to see Koyo-chan's ears go "boing", and maybe sparkling eyes too?
ぴこーん、なった！
Boing, they did it!
うわーー！かわいいーー！
Whoa! So cute!
実際もっとぴこーんってなるのがあるんだよ
Actually, there's one where they boing even more.
え、なになに、触れるんですか？
Eh, what? Can we touch them?
びっくりしちゃった！
I was surprised!
さあーーー！びっくりーー！
Here we go! SURPRISE!
めっちゃぴこしとる！
They're boinging so much!
どこ、どこで吸えますか、その耳！
Where, where can I inhale those ears?!
さあ、こよりのアタマで吸いすぎないでな！
Now, don't inhale Koyo's head too much!
てことで、みんな色んなポーズさせてくれてありがとう！
Anyway, thanks for letting me do all those poses!
ありがとう！めっちゃ死ぬ、かわいい
Thank you! I'm dying, so cute.
ありがとう！このあとも頑張るね！
Thank you! I'll do my best for the rest too!
頑張るぞ！ありがとうございます！
Let's go! Thank you so much!
魅せるぞ！こより！かわいいよー！
Show us what you've got, Koyori! You're cute!
あーかわいいかわいい、もっとちょうだい！
Ah, cute, cute, give me more!
ありがとうございます
Thank you very much.
ということで、なんか受け取った最後ファンの人が「ありがとうございます」って言って受け取っていた気がするけど
So, I feel like at the end there, a fan said "thank you" while taking it.
ホロックスのみんなに来てもらいましたー！
We had everyone from HoloX join us!
色んなポーズさせてもらえたね
I got to do all sorts of poses.
さすが、さすがやはり、こよの仲間、よう分かっておる
As expected of Koyo's comrades, they know me well.
では、続きまして...
Now, moving on...
仲間ではなく、先輩から色んなこと聞いたら、さらにいいポーズができちゃうんじゃないかってことで
Not just comrades, I thought I could do even better poses if I asked my seniors.
この方々をお呼びしようと思います！
So, I'd like to call upon these people!
カナリアーノのお二人ーーー！
The two from Kanariano!
いぇーーい！
Yaaaay!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
先輩だ！先輩！
It's our seniors! Seniors!
あー食べたくなっちゃう、かわいい！
Ah, I want to eat her up, so cute!
（絶叫と歓声）
(Screaming and cheering)
今日はですね、ゲストからのポーズ指定にそってポーズをとってくれる、ということで...
Today, I'll be taking poses based on the guest's instructions...
ぜひやってくれるって！なんでもやってくれるって本当？
She said she'd definitely do it! Is it true you'll do anything?
本当に？あ、そうです、先輩の言うことだったらなんでもします。
Really? Ah, yes, if it's my seniors' orders, I'll do anything.
おお、なんでも！どうする、かなたさん、なんでもやってくれるって。
Oh, anything! What should we do, Kanata-san? She said she'll do anything.
おお、じゃあ、じゃあ、そうですね... もうちょっとアイドルっぽいポーズを...
Oh, then, well... an idol-like pose...
そうだ、そうだね。とらせようかな、まずは。
That's right. Let's make her do one, first.
ぜひ、先輩からご指導ください。
Please, seniors, give me instructions.
冷静にね。冷静に。冷静にね。
Stay calm. Calmly. Stay calm.
じゃあ、あの、僕がよくやる大好きなアイドルポーズなんですけど...
Okay, well, it's my favorite idol pose that I often do...
両手を前に伸ばして、両手を前に。そうそうそう。
Stretch both hands forward, both hands forward. Yes, yes.
で、ちょっと片足をぴっと上げて、首をコテン、みたいな感じの。
Then, lift one leg slightly and tilt your head 'koten' (cutely).
コテン... ちょっとこれ恥ずかしい...
Koten... This is a bit embarrassing...
可愛い！！バランス感覚すごい！ちょっともうちょっと引いたのも見たいな。
So cute!! Amazing balance! I want to see it from a bit further away too.
足も見たいじゃん、足も！足もぴょってやってほしい！いいね、いいね！
We want to see the legs too, the legs! I want you to go 'pyo'! Good, good!
可愛い！！おお、もっと下からもお願いします。もっと下からも！
So cute!! Oh, from a lower angle too, please. From even lower!
バランス感覚、いいね、いいね！素晴らしい！素晴らしい！あーダメ！
Balance is good, good! Splendid! Splendid! Ah, no!
いや、でも素晴らしい。これがアイドルってことですね。これがアイドルだなぁ。
Wow, splendid. This is what an idol is. This is an idol.
はい、じゃあ、私もいいかな？ぜひ！あの、やっぱりアイドル、我々アイドルの先輩として...
Okay, well, can I go next? Please! As your idol seniors...
やってきた伝統のものがあるので、ちょっとやってもらいたいんですけど。やりたいです！
There's a traditional thing we've done, so I'd like you to do it. I want to do it!
まず後ろを向いてもらって、数歩歩いて、くるって振り向いて何か一言言って。
First, face backwards, walk a few steps, turn around, and say something.
一言... ちょっと待って... うん。
Say something... wait a second... okay.
愛してるぞ。
I love you.
（絶叫）ちょっと、一言難しい... ちょっと前までもおーやだやだ...
(Screaming) Wait, saying something is hard... stop looking at me like that...
そういう無茶振りやめて、フレア！でも可愛いじゃん！後ろもしっかり見てもらいたいからさ。
Stop with those unreasonable requests, Flare! But it's cute! I wanted them to see your back too.
もう全身隈なく見てほしいよね。さすが進行分かってらっしゃる。
I want them to see your whole body. As expected, she knows how to direct.
じゃあ、このカメラをちょっと下に置いて、この下に... いいですね、下に！
Then, put the camera down low. Put it down... That's good, down there!
転んじゃった僕たちに対して「大丈夫？」ってこう近づいてくる、やってほしいです。
Approach us, who have fallen down, and say "Are you okay?" I want you to do that.
転んじゃったの？大丈夫？
Did you fall? Are you okay?
（絶叫）うわ、これめっちゃいい！素晴らしい！最高！
(Screaming) Whoa, this is so good! Wonderful! The best!
昇天したわ、天国まで行きます、ありがとう。ダメ、天国行っちゃダメなんだわ。
I've ascended. I'm going to heaven, thank you. No, you shouldn't go to heaven.
魂飛んでったわ、魂も飛んでったわ。いや最高だなぁ。
My soul flew away. My soul flew away too. Wow, it was the best.
あ、でもさ、まださ、もう一個見せてくれるって聞いたんですけど。もうなんか。
Oh, but wait, I heard you'd show us one more thing. Something else.
そうなんです、ちょっと二人に見せられるらしくて。料理してくれるんじゃないかなって。
That's right, apparently I can show the two of you something. Maybe she'll 'cook' for us.
つけてきますね、こより。料理してくれるのか、何だろうね。いい感じに料理してくれますよ！
Put them on, Koyori. Is she going to cook? I wonder what it is. She'll 'cook' for us nicely!
料理してくれますか、これ！エッロ！エッロ要素が来たぞ！エッロ！すげー待ってた！
Is she going to 'cook' for us! Sexy! A sexy element has arrived! Sexy! I've been waiting for this!
はい、はい、はい！じゃあ、ちょっと僕からいいですか？やっぱこれはね、みんな求めてると思うので。
Yes, yes, yes! Then, can I go first? I think everyone wants this, after all.
まず寝っ転がってもらっていいですか？寝っ転がってもらう！
First, can you lie down for a bit? Lie down!
で、上からちょっと押し倒してる感じでカメラをやってもらって。大丈夫なのかな、それ。
And have the camera like someone is pinning you down from above. Is that okay?
そこで「私、アイドルなんだよ」ってちょっと言ってもらって。
And then, say "I'm an idol, you know."
こよ、アイドルなんだよ。
Koyo is an idol, you know.
（絶叫）ありがとうございまーす！最高！
(Screaming) Thank you! The best!
これアイドルですか？アイドルだよ！アイドルだって必要なんだよ！こより！
Is this an idol? She is an idol! It's necessary for an idol too! Koyori!
そうだ、そうだ。アイドルなんだよって言ったらアイドルですね。じゃあ、ノエル先輩なんかありますか？
That's right. If she says she's an idol, then she's an idol. Noel-senpai, do you have anything?
アイドルのシチュエーションといったらもう僕にお任せ。カメラを下からのアングルにしていただき...
When it comes to idol situations, leave it to me. Have the camera at a low angle...
下から、好きだなあ。大好き。踏んでください。あの、ちょっとドSな感じで踏んでほしいです。
From below, you really like that. Love it. Please step on us. With a bit of a sadistic vibe.
（絶叫）おお、いいぞ！踏んで、踏んで！下から下から！
(Screaming) Oh, nice! Step on us! From below, from below!
下からばっかりで... わあ、変態！変態！あー！
Nothing but low angles... Whoa, perverts! Perverts! Ahh!
ちょっと、これアイドル？ねえ、これアイドルですか？アイドル最高！アイドルだろうが！
Wait, is this an idol? Hey, is this an idol? Idols are the best! Of course it's an idol!
みんなやってきたんだ、先輩たちも！そうだ！全アーカイブ漁るぞ！本当か？
Everyone's done it, even our seniors! Exactly! I'll dig through all the archives! Is it true?
あの、最後に、もう一個私いいですか？どうぞ、どうぞ。近づいてもらって、壁ドンやってもらっていいですか？
Well, can I do one last thing? Go ahead. Could you come close and do a Kabedon?
わかりました。
Understood.
ドン。これがアイドルかちょっと心配になってきたから、カナーリアの二人、またな！
Thud. I'm starting to worry if this is an idol, so you two from Kanaria, see ya!
ありがとうございまーす！大好きだぞ！ありがとうございました！
Thank you! I love you! Thank you very much!
ということで、ちょっと不安になったんで切りました。大丈夫だったかな、これ。
So, I got a bit worried, so I cut them off. I wonder if that was okay.
これこより、あの、指示待ちこよりになってるだけで、こよりに問題はないので、YouTubeさんよろしくお願いします。
This is just "Instruction-waiting Koyo", there's no problem with Koyo herself, so YouTube-san, please be kind.
それでは続きまして、ちょっともっとやばい気がするんですけど...
Now, moving on, I feel like it's going to get even worse...
それでは、
So then,
頭がピンクっぽい皆さんをお呼びしたいと思います！
I'd like to call out everyone with pinkish heads!
頭ピンクっぽい皆さんー！
Everyone with pinkish heads!
にゃっはろー！
Nyhello!
こんまっするー！
Konmuscle!
アッホイ！
Ahoy!
頭？髪の色じゃない？ちょっと船長ほら赤...
Head? Isn't it hair color? Look, Captain's is red...
なるほどなるほど。自分金髪なんですけどいいんですかここにいて？
I see, I see. I'm blonde, is it okay for me to be here?
え、あ、頭の中がピンクかなって...
Uh, I thought maybe your head [mind] was pink...
色んなピンクを味合わせてくれるんじゃないかなって。
I thought you'd give us a taste of various pinks.
あ、じゃお名前よろしくお願いします！
Ah, please introduce yourselves!
はい。えー、エリートみこ、頭がピンク色の髪型、
Yes. Er, Elite Miko, the one with the pink hairstyle,
さくらみこです。
Sakura Miko.
髪型さくらみこ。
Hairstyle Sakura Miko.
アッホイ！えー、頭がピンクすぎてちょっと濃いピンク、
Ahoy! Er, my head was so pink it became dark pink,
いや赤まで行きました、船長まりんです！
no, it went all the way to red, Captain Marine!
船長まりんです！
Captain Marine!
はい！こんまっするー！えー、ちょっと髪の毛もうピンクを通り越して、
Yes! Konmuscle! Er, my hair has already passed pink,
真っ白というか銀髪になってしまった。はい。
and become pure white, or rather, silver. Yes.
ま、中身はね、でも誰よりもピンクだと噂されているノエルです。
Well, as for the inside, I'm Noel, who's rumored to be pinker than anyone.
よろしくお願いします。
Nice to meet you.
今日はもう、こよりのアイドル人生終わらせに来たから。
Today, we've come to end Koyori's idol career.
やめ、やめてやめて！
Stop, stop it!
際どいギリギリ、ギリギリ攻めるぜー！
On the edge, right on the limit, we're going to push it!
やっぱね船長ねちょっと一番ねずっとずっと思ってたことがあって。
You know, Captain has one thing she's been thinking about for a long, long time.
こより、お前の着ているシャツ、それ短いよね、どう考えても。
Koyori, that shirt you're wearing, it's short, no matter how you look at it.
あ、そ、そうですか？洗濯で縮んだ感じかな？
O-Oh, is that so? Maybe it shrunk in the wash?
ウエストが、お姉さん盛り上がっちゃってさ、シャツが捲れ上がっちゃって、
The waist... sister, it's puffed up, the shirt is riding up,
これ、なん、隙間が感じる！
and this... I feel a gap!
どうなっちゃってるのかな？ちょっと3Dだから覗き込めるのかなって。
What's going on? Since it's 3D, I wonder if we can peer inside.
覗き見ないで！見せないで！
Don't peer in! Don't show us!
でもさ、これだったらさあれじゃない？このさ上着ちょっと邪魔じゃないか？
But wait, if that's the case, isn't it? This jacket is a bit in the way, isn't it?
え、邪魔だな！邪魔だな！白衣のこより邪魔だな！
Eh, it's in the way! It's in the way! Lab coat Koyori is in the way!
脱げ！ただのこよりになれ！脱げ！脱げ！脱げ！脱げ！脱げ！脱げ！脱げ！
Take it off! Become just Koyori! Strip! Strip! Strip!
この人たちおじさんだ！でも今までこより脱いだことないから...
These people are old men! But Koyori has never stripped before...
求めてたんだよ、こより。脱げなかったんですよ、今まで。
We've been wanting this, Koyori. You haven't been able to take it off until now.
だから、脱げるわけ！
So, you can take it off!
ああああー！
Aaaaaah!
大丈夫そんな、あ、ちょっと見せてごらん、脇を！脇！
Is it okay... Ah, let's see, show us your armpits! Armpits!
脇見せてごらん。ああー、たまんねぇ！
Show us your armpits. Aah, irresistible!
桃色だよ！桃色だよこの脇！
It's peach-colored! These armpits are peach-colored!
これが脇パイってことですか？
Is this what they call armpit-pie?
やだ、脇がピンクだよこれ。
No way, the armpits are pink.
ちょっと、あの、ほてっちゃってるかもしれないですね、今3Dお披露目で。
Maybe, uh, I'm a bit flushed right now, for the 3D debut.
ほてってるってことはそのさシャツの中も、もしかなり、
If you're flushed, then maybe inside that shirt... is also quite
ほてって、赤くなってんじゃねーかなって。
flushed and red.
行ける？大丈夫？
Can we go? Is it okay?
脱いじゃったほうがいいかな？あ、何だこりゃ！
Maybe it's better to take it off? Oh, what's this!
あー、ちょっと、あー、もうちょっと、もうちょっと！
Ah, a bit... Ah, a bit more, a bit more!
頑張れ！こないのこれ、大丈夫これ？
Do your best! It's not coming, is this okay?
拡大、拡大！もっと！
Zoom in, zoom in! More!
ジャンプとかしたら捲れないかな？
If you jump, won't it ride up?
あ、まずジャンプ！ジャンプしろ、ジャンプしろ！
Ah, first, jump! Jump, jump!
ジャンプしろ！
Jump!
ジャンプ、ちょっと待って、こより、これ、張り付いてる！
Jump, wait, Koyori, this... it's stuck!
色んな危険が。あ、張り付いてるのこれ。
Various dangers. Ah, it's stuck.
捲れないか。
It won't ride up.
あれじゃ、あの、ブリ、ブリッジしろ、ブリッジ！ブリッジ！ねえ！
Then, uh, bri... do a bridge, bridge! Bridge! Hey!
え、ホロライブといえばブリッジまである。
Eh, when you think of Hololive, there's even the bridge.
こよりのブリッジ見せて。できるかな、ブリッジ。
Show us Koyori's bridge. I wonder if I can... bridge.
行け！うわああー！上がった！
Go! Uwaaaa! It's up!
上がった！見えた！見える！
It's up! We saw it! We can see it!
中身見える！
We can see inside!
このあばらいいじゃん、あばらが。浮き出てるあばらが、あ、健康的！
These ribs are great, the ribs. The protruding ribs are, ah, healthy!
膨らみが見えるよ。なんかある、これ！なんかある！
You can see the bulge. There's something here! There's something!
なんかある、山が二つ！山だろ！
There's something, two mountains! They're mountains!
あるんですよ。
There are.
素晴らしいですね。いや、上半身もいいけど、ちょっと下半身もよくないですか？
Wonderful. No, the upper body is good, but isn't the lower body also good?
このタイツ。
These tights.
あ、気づいちゃいました？
Ah, did you notice?
あ、いいですね！黒くなって、なんか濃く、あ、なんかヒールがすごい。あ、いいね。
Ah, they're nice! They're black and somewhat dark, oh, the heels are amazing. Ah, nice.
なまめかしいね、デニールいいですね。
Sultry, the denier is good.
デニールちょっとよく見たいな、もうちょっとよく見たい。もうちょっと、もうちょっと。
I want to see the denier a bit better, a bit better. A bit more, a bit more.
もうちょっと、もうちょっと。
A bit more, a bit more.
うわ、なんか卑らしい、お、なんか卑らしい、このハイヒール。
Whoa, somehow lewd, oh, somehow lewd, these high heels.
卑らしいハイヒール。
Lewd high heels.
もう、おー！あ、この境目が。濃くなっていく境目が。
Geez, oh! Ah, this border. The border where it gets darker.
これ、影がえ、エロい。自覚、自覚している！
This, the shadow is, er, erotic. Conscious, you're conscious of it!
いい、このこよ。一番頭がピンクだからな。
Nice, this Koyo. Since her head is the pinkest.
いやいやいや、ピンクなのは髪型だけですよ。
No, no, no, only the hairstyle is pink.
いやいや、でも頭ピンク組ですもんね。
No, no, but you're part of the pink-head group, right?
こより、求めてたんですんよね、これを。
Koyori, you've been wanting this, haven't you?
あ、そうなんです、皆さん。だから、
Ah, that's right, everyone. So,
こちらにさ、ポーズ指示させて、本当は自分でやりたい
you're letting us give pose instructions, but don't you actually have
ピンクのポーズがあるんじゃないの？
a pink pose you want to do yourself?
やれと言ったろ！
I told you to do it!
トントンして！
Do the tapping!
背中見せてみろや！
Let's see your back!
えっ、背中？
Wait, my back?
背中！
Back!
え、そこで、そっからさ、ほら、よく...
Um, there, from there, like how...
あの、手をさ地面に付ける、足を真っ直ぐにしてさ、
you put your hands on the ground with your legs straight,
こう、美脚をアピールするポーズ。
a pose that highlights your legs.
あ、マリン先輩がよくやるやつや！
Ah, the one Marine-senpai often does!
こういう？こういうこと？
Like this? Is this what you mean?
かわいい！
So cute!
あら、かわいい。
Oh, how cute.
しっぽもいいわね！
The tail is good too!
しっぽいいな。
I like the tail.
こんなポーズいいわね！
This is a great pose!
思い付かないですよ、やっぱ先輩たちはピンクだなあ！
I couldn't have thought of that. You seniors are really lewd!
いやいやいや、こっち側だろ。
No, no, no, you're one of us.
助かるわ、後輩よ。
Thanks for the help, junior.
いや、これからもぜひ、あのピンクなものに、色々伝授していただければと...
Well, I'd love for you to keep teaching me all sorts of lewd things...
...思っております、先輩方に。
...from now on, seniors.
任せなさいよ。
Leave it to us.
任せなさいよ！
Leave it to us!
伝授するわよ。
We'll teach you everything.
ありがとうございます！色々格好もさせていただき、脱がせてもいただきまして...
Thank you so much! I got to do various poses and even had some clothes taken off...
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
お披露目頑張ってね！
Good luck with the showcase!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ありがとうございます、頑張ります！
Thank you, I'll do my best!
見てるからね！
We'll be watching!
また！
See you!
はあはあ、というわけで、えー、頭ピンク組の皆さんに、ちょっと身ぐるみを剥がされてしまいました。
Whew, so, I've had my clothes practically stripped by the lewd-minded group.
さあ皆さん、ちょっとゲストの皆さんによって色んなポーズしたわけですけど、
Well everyone, I did various poses thanks to the guests, but...
スクショバッチリ撮れたかな？
did you manage to get some good screenshots?
撮れた？
Did you?
撮れたっぽいですね！
Looks like you did!
ではでは！この検証は成功！ということで。
So then! This experiment was a success!
えー、最初にお話ししてました、このラボのとある機能、お披露目しちゃいたいと思いまーす！
Now, I'd like to unveil that 'certain feature' of this lab I mentioned at the beginning!
それでは、機能のお披露目とともに、2曲続けて歌って踊っちゃおうと思うのでお聞きください！
Now, along with the unveiling of the feature, I'm going to sing and dance to two songs in a row!
どうぞ！
Here you go!
誇り高きアイドル
Prideful Idol
作詞：shito, Gom 作曲：shito
Lyrics: shito, Gom / Composition: shito
私のこと知ってますか？ 可愛く見えてますか？
Do you know about me? Do I look cute to you?
私の歌どうだろうな うまく歌えてますか？
What do you think of my singing? Am I singing well?
衣装だとかメイクだとか 可愛く見えてますか？
The costume, the makeup... Do I look cute to you?
振付とかファンサとかも 喜んでもらえますか？
The choreography, the fan service... Are you happy with them?
手は冷たくなって 足は震える
My hands turn cold, my legs tremble
それでも戦いたい アイドルだから
But I still want to fight, because I'm an idol
バカにする奴は嫌いだ
I hate those who make fun of us
見下されるのも嫌いだ
I hate being looked down upon too
“アイドルなんか”という言葉を 見てもいないくせに言うな
Don't say 'it's just an idol' when you haven't even seen us
頑張りを当然と言うな
Don't call our hard work 'natural'
イメージとか強制するな
Don't force your image on us
“アイドルなんか”という言葉は この世で一番大嫌いだ
The phrase 'it's just an idol' is what I hate most in this world
プライベート見えないから 分からないと思います
You can't see my private life, so I don't think you'd know
性格とか悪い方です 騙しちゃっていますか？
My personality is actually on the bad side. Am I deceiving you?
でも本気です 本気なんです ありのままの私を
But I'm serious, I really am. My true self...
好きになって推して下さい それってワガママですか？
...please come to love and support me. Is that selfish of me?
きっと可愛くない 全部わかってる
I'm sure I'm not cute, I know all that
それでも好かれてたい アイドルだから
But I still want to be liked, because I'm an idol
皮肉言う奴は嫌いだ
I hate those who say sarcastic things
言い訳ばかりも嫌いだ
I hate constant excuses too
“こんなもんか”という言葉を 軽々しく口にするな
Don't say 'is that all you've got?' so lightly
勝手に限界決めるな
Don't decide our limits for us
笑い者になんてするな
Don't make a laughing stock of us
“アイドルなんか”という言葉は この世で一番大嫌いだ
The phrase 'it's just an idol' is what I hate most in this world
向かい風を切り裂け
Cut through the headwind
誇り高きアイドル
The prideful idol
（目指そうぜ）
(Let's aim for it!)
応援がなければ
Without support,
活動できない
I can't continue my activities.
好きな事ばかりじゃ
I can't live by just
生きてはいけない
doing what I like.
元気あげるはずが
I'm supposed to give energy,
もらってばかりだし
but I'm always receiving it.
恩返しできる日まで
Wait for me until the day
待ってて
I can repay the favor.
こよちゃんに出逢ってから人生が変わったよ
My life changed after meeting Koyo-chan.
初めて自分から好きだと言える存在に出逢えた
I met someone I can say I love for the first time.
夢を全部叶える、助手くんと一緒なら
I'll fulfill all my dreams if I'm with Joshu-kun.
歓声が減っても
Even if the cheers decrease,
飽きられちゃっても
even if people get tired of me.
それでも笑っていたい
I still want to keep smiling,
アイドルだから
because I'm an idol.
熱いファンの愛があって
With the love of passionate fans,
スタッフさんの愛があって
with the love of the staff,
いつも家族の愛があって
always with the love of my family,
生きてる
I am living.
“アイドル”
"Idol."
バカにする奴は嫌いだ
I hate people who make fun of us.
見下されるのも嫌いだ
I hate being looked down upon too.
“アイドルなんか”という言葉を
The words "just an idol",
見てもいないくせに言うな
don't say them when you haven't even seen us.
頑張りを当然と言うな
Don't say our efforts are to be expected.
イメージとか強制するな
Don't force images on us.
“アイドルなんか”という言葉は
The words "just an idol" are
この世で一番大嫌いだ
what I hate most in this world.
一番の宝物
The Most Precious Treasure
裾が濡れたなら
If the hem gets wet,
乾くの待てばいい
I just have to wait for it to dry.
水音をたてて跳ねた
I splashed and jumped.
きみが教えてくれたんだ
You taught me,
もう怖くない
I'm not afraid anymore.
握っていてくれた
I must let go of this hand
この手を離さなきゃだめだ
that you held for me.
ひとりでもゆくよ
I will go on alone,
たとえ辛くても
even if it's hard.
みんなで見た夢は
I will definitely take the dreams
必ず持ってくよ
we saw together with me.
みんなとがいいな
I wish I could be with everyone.
みんなとがよかった
I'm glad I was with everyone.
でも目覚めた朝
But on the morning I woke up,
誰も居ないんだね
nobody was there.
もう振り返っても
Even if I look back now,
誰の影もない
there's no one's shadow.
水たまりだけが光った
Only the puddles were shining.
生きてくこと　それは
Living means
立ち向かっていくこと
facing things head-on.
それがわかったなら
If I understand that,
あとは踏み出す勇気だけ
all that's left is the courage to step forward.
どこまでもゆくよ
I will go anywhere,
ここで知ったこと
with what I learned here.
幸せという夢を
I'll show you I can make the dream
叶えてみせるよ
of happiness come true.
みんなと離れても
Even if I'm separated from everyone,
どんなに遠くなっても
no matter how far away I get.
新しい朝に
In the new morning,
この僕は生きるよ
I will live.
ひとりでもゆくよ
I'll go on alone,
死にたくなっても
even if I want to die.
声が聞こえるよ
I can hear a voice,
死んではいけないと
telling me I mustn't die.
たとえ辛くても
Even if it's painful,
闇に閉ざされても
even if I'm shut away in darkness,
心の奥には
deep within my heart,
明かりが灯ってるよ
a light is shining.
巡って流れて
Moving and flowing,
時は移ろいだ
time has shifted.
もう何があったか
I can't remember
思い出せないけど
what happened anymore, but...
目を閉じみれば
if I close my eyes,
みんなの笑い声
I hear everyone's laughter.
なぜかそれが今
For some reason, that is now
一番の宝物
my most precious treasure.
はーい！
Yes! (Laughs)
ということで、
And so,
誇り高きアイドル、一番の宝物、
"Hokori Takaki Idol" and "Ichiban no Takaramono,"
2曲続けてお聞きいただきました！
you just heard two songs in a row!
どうだったかなー？
How was it?
えー、みんな「誇り高きアイドル」の前に、
Before "Hokori Takaki Idol,"
コヨラボがバーンなってバーンなったの見てくれた？
did you see the Koyo-Lab go "bam" and "bam"?
すごいでしょ！
Amazing, right?
あのラボはですね、なんとステージ転換をすることによって
That lab, believe it or not, by changing the stage,
ライブステージになることができるんです！
can actually become a live stage!
イエーイ！
Yay!
えー、こよの、あの、ライブステージでちょっとこよのあの
I wanted to sing with that
泥臭いアイドル感を歌いたいなと思って「誇り高きアイドル」、
"gritty idol" feel of mine on my live stage, so I sang "Hokori Takaki Idol."
そして、あの、ちょっと、へ、歌えるなら歌いたいなってなって、
And, well, I really wanted to sing this if I could,
あの大好きなね、Angel Beats!の「一番の宝物」歌わせていただきましたー！
my favorite song, "Ichiban no Takaramono" from Angel Beats!
歌わせていただきました！
I sang it for you!
さてさて、続いてなんですけど、
Now then, moving on...
こよ、あのデビューした時から
Ever since my debut,
この曲を歌いたいけど、勇気が持てたら歌う、
there's been a song I've wanted to sing, but only when I have the courage.
って言ってる曲が1曲ずっとあったと思うんですよ。
I think I've mentioned it before.
で、その曲を歌いたいなーって思うんですが、
And I really want to sing that song,
まだちょっと3Dになっても自信が持ちきれないんです。
but even in 3D, I'm still not quite confident enough.
なので、あるチャレンジに成功することができたら、
So, if I can succeed in a certain challenge,
アイドルとして一歩成長できるんじゃないかなって思って。
I thought I might be able to grow a step further as an idol.
それでちょっとチャレンジしようと思うんだけど、
So I'm going to take on a challenge.
みんな応援してくれるかな？
Will you all support me?
いい？
Is that okay?
Is it?
うん、おーおーって言ってるみんな。
Yeah, everyone's saying "oh oh."
いいかな？じゃあこよ頑張るね！
All right then? Then Koyo will do her best!
挑戦見届けてください！
Please watch over my challenge!
では挑戦するところに行くよー！
Now, I'm off to the challenge!
えー、飛行機に乗ってブーーーン...
Taking a plane, vroom...
着陸！
Landing!
ってことで、サバンナに帰ってきましたー！
And so, I'm back in the savanna!
イエーイ！
Yay!
お、なんかいる！お、なんかおるな。
Oh, there's something there! Oh, there's something, isn't there?
えー実家である、こよの実家...
This is my hometown, my childhood home...
サバンナに帰ってきましたー！
I've returned to the savanna!
ここではこのコーナーをやろうと思います！
I'm going to do this segment here!
こよりのアイドルチャレンジ！
Koyori's Idol Challenge!
イェーイ！
Yay!
こよりのアイドルチャレンジ！
Koyori's Idol Challenge!
ちょっと遠くにちょこちょこいる動物がちょっと気になるんですけども。
I'm a little concerned about the animals moving around in the distance, but...
それではですね、あのアイドルというものは
Well then, I know that...
いつでも体を張らなければいけない生き物だとこよりはあの知っております。
...idols are creatures who must always put their bodies on the line.
なのでこのサバンナでいくつかのチャレンジで体を張っていこうと思います。
So, I'm going to put my body on the line with several challenges in this savanna.
で今から3つチャレンジをするんですけども、
I'm going to do three challenges from now,
その中の1つでも成功することができたらアイドルとしてレベルアップできたよということで、
and if I can succeed in even one of them, it means I've leveled up as an idol,
さっき言ってた曲を歌いたいなと思います！
so I'd like to sing the song I mentioned earlier!
っていうのをこよが考えてたんですけど、
That's what Koyo was thinking,
なんかね、なんかあのスタッフさんが一個ちょっと要素を増やしてたんですよ。
but somehow, the staff added one little element.
なんか、なんかちょっとあのさっき言ってたやつ出してもらっていいですか？
Can you, like, bring out the thing you were talking about earlier?
ねぇなんか出ちゃったんですけど！
Hey, something appeared!
野生 / 人間
Wild / Human
あの、なぜかですねこのサバンナ、あの魔術がかけられておりまして、
Um, for some reason, this savanna has been cursed with magic,
なんとチャレンジに失敗すると、この人間な姿のこよりから野生に帰ってしまうらしいんですよ！
and apparently, if I fail a challenge, I'll return to the wild from this human-form Koyori!
えっちょ、えっどういうこと？
Wait, um, what does that mean?
え、まだ動きはないのかな？
Eh, is there no movement yet?
（遠吠え）
(Howling)
ちょっと吠えたくなったわ！ちょっと吠えたくなった、どうして！？今まだ、まだ失敗してない！
I felt like howling a bit! I felt like howling a bit, why!? I haven't failed yet!
はいはいはい、戻れた戻れた。よかったよかった。
Okay, okay, okay, I'm back. Good, good.
とわけで、このね、野生に帰ったらちょっとこよりそのままサバンナに置いてけぼりになっちゃう可能性もあるんで、成功できるように頑張っていこうと思います！
So, if I return to the wild, I might just be left behind in the savanna, so I'll do my best to succeed!
では1つ目のチャレンジはこちら！
Now, the first challenge is this!
真剣白羽取りならぬ、真剣ふがし取り！
Not a serious sword catch, but a serious fugashi catch!
はい、ということでですね、えーオープニングでも歌っている通り、
Right, so, as I sang in the opening,
ちなみにふがしは空気ですということでこよはふがしが大好きです。
by the way, "fugashi is air," and Koyo loves fugashi.
そんなふがしを今回、作ってもらいました！
We had such a fugashi made this time!
ジャジャジャジャーン！デン！
Ta-da! Bam!
見覚えのあるこのなんかパーキングエリアでよく売られているお土産のこのふがし棒！
This familiar fugashi stick often sold as a souvenir at parking areas!
え、これを、まふがしは空気なので当たっても痛くないやろーってことで、
Well, since fugashi is air, it shouldn't hurt if it hits me, so...
え、みんなにね、真剣のようにちょっとこよを狙ってもらおうと思います。
I'll have you all aim at Koyo like it's a real sword.
おおーやる気だね助手くん。
Oh, you're motivated, Josh-kun.
じゃ、じゃ助手くん、あの「えいっ」ってコメントで言ってもらっていいですか？「えいっ」てね。
Then, Josh-kun, can you say "Ei!" in the comments? "Ei!"
よし、絶対受け止めてやるからよ。行くぞ！
Alright, I'll definitely catch it. Here I go!
ラウンドワン！
Round 1!
まだ、ラウンドワンって言ってないじゃん助手くん。
Wait, I haven't said "Round 1" yet, Josh-kun.
ねぇラウンドワンって今言おうとしたの。ねぇ、痛いよ。
Hey, I was just about to say "Round 1." Hey, that hurts.
空気のはずなのに。まあまあまあ、いいですよ。
It's supposed to be air. Well, whatever.
助手くんはちょっと先走っちゃうところもありますからね。
Josh-kun tends to jump the gun sometimes.
ラウンド2行くよラウンド2、はい。ラウンド2、来い！
Let's go to Round 2, Round 2. Okay. Round 2, come at me!
えっ、痛っ！
Eh, ouch!
ねぇ早い、助手くん早い！
Hey, too fast, Josh-kun is too fast!
あ、あ、あ、ちょっと、あ、野生の血が滾ってきた。
Ah, ah, ah, wait, ah, my wild blood is boiling.
クーッ！
Kuh!
よしじゃ、3回目勝負ということで、これラストチャンスで。お願いします。えい、えい、よろしく。
Alright then, for the third match, this is the last chance. Please. Ei, ei, good luck.
行くよ！
Going!
せーの！
Ready, set...
おお、掴めた！掴めたー！
Oh, I caught it! I caught it!
え、これ成功？成功、成功ですよね？
Eh, is this a success? Success, it's a success, right?
やっ、やったー！助手くん、ちょっと最後手加減しちゃったんじゃないの？
Ya-yay! Josh-kun, didn't you go a bit easy at the end?
やったー！え、じゃあもうこよりアイドルとして一歩成長できた、ん？
Yay! Well, then Koyori has grown one step further as an idol, huh?
あ、でも2対1か。そっか。
Ah, but it's 2 to 1. I see.
2対1だから、まあなんか、ちゃんと勝ったって感じが、まあせえへんか。そっか。
It's 2 to 1, so, well, it doesn't really feel like I properly won. I see.
じゃ、じゃあとりあえず一応成功した感はあるんですけど、
Well, well, anyway, I feel like I've succeeded for now, but...
2個目のチャレンジもいこうと思います！
I'm going to go for the second challenge too!
バレたかーって言ってる助手くん、やっぱ手加減してくれたん、優しいなぁ。
Josh-kun is saying "I've been caught," as expected he went easy on me, so kind.
ではではでは、続いてのチャレンジはこちら！
Now, now, now, the next challenge is this!
ぶら下がり1分チャレンジ！イェーイ！
Hanging for 1 minute challenge! Yay!
ということで、サバンナにぶら下がれるものを立てようとしていますが、立ちません！
So, I'm trying to set up something to hang from in the savanna, but it won't stand!
立てて、立てて、ぶら下がれるやつ立てて。立たないよ！
Stand up, stand up, set up the hanging thing. It's not standing!
立たないですよ！じゃあ空気にぶら下がろうかな。
It's not standing! Well then, maybe I'll hang from the air.
あ、いけた、いけた。きたきたきた、よかったよかった。
Ah, I did it, I did it. It's here, here, here, good, good.
ということでね、今のふがしを使って、えーなんかちょっと鉄棒みたいなやつを作りました！
So, using the fugashi from just now, I made something like a pull-up bar!
ははっ！よかった、立ってくれて。
Haha! I'm glad it stood up.
で、これにね、ちょっとね、ぶら下がりたいなと思うんですけども。
So, I'm thinking I'd like to hang from this for a bit...
あの、やったことあんまりないんですけど、多分楽勝だと思うんですよ。
I haven't done it much, but I think it'll be a breeze.
なんであのぶら下がってるだけだとつまんないと思うんで、
Since just hanging there would be boring...
助手くん何か質問とかコメント欄で書いてくれたらこより答えるので。
if you write some questions in the comments, Koyori will answer them.
はい、じゃあやってこうと思います。
Okay, let's give it a try.
せーの！
Ready, set...!
あ、あ、あ、野生の血が…わ、わ、わ！
Ah! My wild blood is... wa, wa, wa!
24秒、結構頑張った方なんだけどこれはきつかった。
24 seconds. I worked pretty hard, but that was really tough.
でも一個、一個スリスー…聞いてたの答えられたよ。
But I was able to answer one question that I heard.
答え、答えたけどこれは失敗ということは…
I answered it, but if this counts as a failure...
あれ？
Huh?
あれ、今なんか変なのつかないわ？あれ？
Huh? Didn't something strange just happen? Huh?
やばい！野生に若干戻り始めているわん！
Oh no! I'm starting to revert to the wild a bit, woof!
これは、これはどうしようもないわん。
This, this can't be helped, woof.
次のチャレンジに行くわん！
I'll move on to the next challenge, woof!
次のチャレンジはバランスチャレンジわんわんわん！
The next challenge is the Balance Challenge, woof woof woof!
お、あ、あ、あ、こよりの遊び道具出てきた。わーわーわーわー！
Oh! Koyori's plaything has appeared. Woof-woof-woof-woof!
違うんや。違う、違う、野生じゃないわん。
No, that's wrong. No, no, I'm not wild, woof.
ということでこちらはこちらですね、こよりが作ったバランスを…
So, this is a balance...
こうぽよんぽよんと、あの、やることのできる…
thingy that Koyori made where you can go "boing, boing"...
何言ってるか分からなくなってきたわん。
I'm losing track of what I'm saying, woof.
バランスをね、あの、保つことのできる爆弾です！イェイ！
It's a bomb that you can use to maintain balance! Yay!
これルマの感想でもやってましたね、爆発ね。ああ。
We did the explosion thing in the Luma impressions, too. Ah.
これに乗って10秒耐えることができたらチャレンジ成功ということで。
If I can stay on this for 10 seconds, the challenge is a success.
やってみようと思いますわん。いくよ！
So I'll give it a try, woof. Here I go!
いけるやろ、バランスボール。
I should be able to do it, it's just a balance ball.
さー、いくぞ！せーの！
Okay, here I go! Ready, set...!
ぽん、ぽん、わー！
Boing, boing, wa-!
これもしかして今こより、あの人間じゃなくなってるから、
Maybe since Koyori isn't human right now...
あの四足のつもりでやったほうがええんか、わん？
it'd be better if I did it as a four-legged animal, woof?
ということわん？
Is that how it works, woof?
じゃあちょっと腹這いでラストチャレンジやらせてくださいわ。
Then let me try the last challenge on my stomach, woof.
10秒、10秒こっちならいけるかもしれないわん。いくばん！
If it's this way, I might last 10 seconds, woof. Here I go!
せーの！
Ready, set!
あ、ちょっと戻ったわ。
Ah, I came back a bit.
やばい、もう日本語を喋れなくなってしまったわん。
Oh no, I've already become unable to speak Japanese, woof.
ということでこのままではアイドルの曲を歌うとかそういうわけにもいかないので、
At this rate, I won't be able to sing idol songs or anything like that.
こんな時こそ前に開発しておいたあの薬を使いたいと思うわん。
At a time like this, I want to use that medicine I developed before, woof.
人間じゃないものになってしまった時に人間に戻るための薬、
Medicine to return to human form when you've become something non-human.
いでよわん！
Come forth, woof!
あれ？一個しかないはずなのになんか一杯あるわ。
Huh? There should only be one set, but there are a lot, woof.
嗅覚が今冴え渡ってるから匂いで嗅げばわかるはずわん。
My sense of smell is sharp now, so I should be able to tell by the scent, woof.
くんくん…これはなんか泥臭い匂いがするわ。
Sniff... This one has a kind of muddy smell, woof.
こっちは？
How about this one?
うん、これはちょっとフレッシュでなんかオレンジみたいな香りがするわ。
Yeah, this is a bit fresh and smells like oranges, woof.
次。
Next.
あー、これ甘くて色もちょっとこより色だし可愛い香りがするわ。
Oh, this is sweet and the color is a bit like Koyori's color, and it has a cute scent, woof.
次。
Next.
あ、美味しそう。美味しそうなの…あー！出た出た！
Ah, looks delicious. It looks... ah! It came out!
飲もうかなと思ったら急に出てきたんだけど。
I was thinking of drinking it and it suddenly came out.
びっくりさせるなよー！
Don't scare me like that!
ということで、これはね
So anyway, this is...
こより色の試験管が世界一やろ
Koyori-colored test tubes are the best in the world, right?
ちょっとおいしそう
It looks kind of tasty.
よーっし
Alright.
いくわん、飲むわん
Here I go-wan, drinking-wan.
はぁー！
Phew!
元に、戻れましたー！
I'm back to normal!
はい、アイドルに戻ってくることができました！
Yes, I was able to return to being an idol!
みんな、ただいま！
Everyone, I'm back!
生き返ったー！生き返っとる
I've come back to life! I'm revived.
ということで、あれこれこよりのアイドルチャレンジ
So, with this and that, Koyori's idol challenge...
一発撮りで一回成功したけどなんか
I succeeded once on the first take, but somehow...
成功感があんまない、ないですかね？
It doesn't really feel like a success, does it?
チャレンジ成功した？したかな？
Was the challenge a success? Did I do it?
ね、成功したってことでいいよね？助手くん
Hey, it's okay to say it was a success, right? Joshu-kun.
いいよね？不正じゃないよ。いいよね？
Right? It's not cheating. Right?
オッケー？
Okay?
うん、あ、助手くんやっぱ優しい、ありがとう！
Yeah, ah, Joshu-kun is kind after all, thank you!
いいよ、ありがとう！
It's fine, thank you!
じゃあ、ちゃんとアイドルとして清楚できたってことで
Well then, since I was able to be 'pure' as an idol,
ラボに戻ってあの曲を歌いたいと思います！
I want to go back to the lab and sing that song!
戻るよー。さあ飛行機に乗るぞー
I'm going back. Now, let's get on the plane!
コヨは、コヨビだよ
Koyo is, Koyo-bi!
せーの、コヨラボです！
One, two, it's Koyo-Lab!
はい、ハッシュタグこより実験中
Yes, hashtag Koyori under experiment!
したっけオッケー
Then it's okay!
コヨは、ズボ、ズボラボです！
Koyo is... Zubo, Zubo-Lab!
はい、やったー
Yes, hooray!
こより実験中、てれーん
Koyori under experiment, ta-da!
やったー、間に合ったー
Hooray, I made it in time!
マヨネーズは飲み物です
Mayonnaise is a drink.
ちなみにブラショ好きで
By the way, I like black ginger.
はい、お肉、全開
Yes, meat, full throttle!
冷凍うどんは常備しています。そうでしたっけ？
I always have frozen udon. Was that it?
はい、やったー、証明完了 Q.E.D.
Yes, hooray, proof complete Q.E.D.
ココだろココ、いやっほー
It's here, right here, yee-haw!
こよりには助手くんのラボ
Koyori has Joshu-kun's lab!
お嬢様、うい、うい、うい
My lady, oui, oui, oui!
おらー、諦めませんよ
Hey, I won't give up!
持ってますもん、そう、そう
I've got it, yes, yes!
うふふ、うふふ、清楚
Ufufu, ufufu, pure!
はい、オッケー
Yes, okay!
ひゅー、やったー
Whew, hooray!
それでは！勇気が出た時に歌うよと言っていたあの曲
Now then! That song I said I'd sing when I gathered my courage...
ホロライブの全体曲、聴いてください！
Hololive's group song, please listen!
Shiny Smily Story!
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to keep seeing the same future
あの夢手にしたい
I want to grasp that dream
それぞれ違ったココロで 走れ GO
With our respective different hearts, run GO
どこを見ても真っ暗な場所に芽生えてた
It sprouted in a place that was pitch black no matter where I looked
ほんの小さな希望にこの瞳奪われた
My eyes were captured by a tiny hope
不安で揺れる心を上手くチューニングして
Finely tuning my heart that wavers with anxiety
ほんの小さな勇気を振り絞っていたよ
I was squeezing out a tiny bit of courage
諦めの文字デリートして進む
Deleting the word 'giving up' and moving forward
苦しいときも、もう私はひとりじゃないから
Because even in painful times, I'm no longer alone
だからもっと夢追いかけたい
So I want to chase my dreams even more
ワクワク止まらない
The excitement won't stop
想像越えてく世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that exceeds your imagination
アクセスしてみたい
I want to try to access it
後悔なんてそうさせない
I won't let you have any regrets
それぞれ違ったココロで 走れ GO
With our respective different hearts, run GO
仮想の空に輝く眩しい想いは
The dazzling feelings shining in the virtual sky
見たことのない光を...
A light never seen before...
見たことのない光を
A light you've never seen before
現実(リアル)に届けるよ
I'll deliver it to reality
いつも聞こえるエールはここにキャプチャーして
Capturing the cheers I always hear right here
また新しい光を
Searching for a new light
探したくなるよ
Once again
君の笑顔は保存して進む
I'll save your smile and move forward
悲しいときに見返すよ
I'll look back at it when I'm sad
力が湧くから
Because it gives me strength
胸を張って夢追いかけたい
I want to chase my dreams with pride
奇跡の物語(ストーリー)
A miraculous story
一緒に作ろう
Let's create it together
終わらない夢を
A dream that never ends
誰一人欠かせない
Everyone is indispensable
愛が満ちたこの世界
In this world filled with love
それぞれ違ったココロで
With each of our different hearts
彩れ
Color it in
悲しいときも 寂しいときも
When I'm sad, or when I'm lonely
信じ合えるものがある
There's something we can believe in together
忘れずにこの鼓動鳴らし続けたい
I want to keep this heartbeat going without forgetting
終わらない世界に溢れ出すよ
It will overflow into an endless world
笑顔達
All these smiles
憧れの舞台立ちたい
I want to stand on the stage I've longed for
らしく輝きたい
I want to shine in my own way
時に涙して
Sometimes shedding tears
また笑い合いたい
I want to laugh together again
同じ未来を見たい
I want to see the same future
あの夢手にしたい
I want to grasp that dream
踏み出そう
Let's step forward
奇跡の
To a miraculous
一歩を
first step
息切らして夢追いかけたい
I want to chase my dreams until I'm breathless
ワクワク止まらない
The excitement won't stop
想像超えてく
Exceeding expectations
世界見せてあげる
I'll show you the world
アクセスしてみない？
Won't you try accessing it?
後悔なんてここにはない
There's no such thing as regret here
それぞれ違ったココロで
With each of our different hearts
作るWORLD
creating a WORLD
はーい！やっと歌えた「Shiny Smily Story」でした！
Hi! That was "Shiny Smily Story," finally performed!
みんな、どうだったかなー！
Everyone, how was it?!
いやむちゃくちゃもうね、ちょっと感慨深くなっちゃって、自分の中でちょっと今クライマックスなんだけども、
Man, I'm just so overwhelmed with emotion right now, it's like I'm at the climax of the show already...
まだまだ、終わらないんだよ！
But it's not over yet!
なんと「重大告知あり」ってサムネに書いてありましたからね！
After all, the thumbnail did say there would be a "Major Announcement"!
それを言うまでは終わりませんが、えーここでちょっとお知らせです！
It's not over until I say it, but first, I have a few other announcements!
まずは、HoloXがどんどん3D化されておりますが、
First, as more and more HoloX members are getting their 3D models...
次に3Dになるのは...こいつだ！
The next one to go 3D is... this person!
鷹嶺ルイ 3Dお披露目
Takane Lui 3D Reveal
次は、HoloXの女幹部、鷹嶺ルイが
Next, HoloX's executive officer, Takane Lui,
6月21日火曜日20時から3Dお披露目配信を行います！
will be holding her 3D debut stream on Tuesday, June 21st at 8:00 PM!
みんな一緒に見に行こうぜ！
Let's all go watch it together!
このお尻が...お尻いいよねｗ
This butt... the butt is great, isn't it? lol
はい！そして、こよりからのちょっとしたお知らせです！どうぞ！
Okay! And now, a small announcement from Koyori! Here it is!
はい、メン限で本日23時から配信を行うのですが、
I'll be doing a membership-exclusive stream today at 11:00 PM,
早速おうち3Dを使って3Dで配信をしようと思っております！
and I'm planning to use my home 3D setup for it right away!
打ち上げ撮影会でいろいろやってみようかなあと思ってるので、
I'm thinking of doing various things for an after-party photoshoot,
一緒に、一緒に23時から楽しみましょう！
so let's enjoy it together starting at 11:00 PM!
そして！次が重大告知だー！デデン！
And now! The major announcement! Ta-da!
ということで！なんと、博衣こより、初めてのオリジナル曲を作りましたー！
So! Believe it or not, Hakui Koyori has made her first original song!
WAO!! Hakui Koyori 1st Original Song
イエーイ！こちらのオリジナル曲、DECO*27さんに作っていただいた、
Yay! This original song was composed by DECO*27,
こよりらしさがいっぱい詰まった曲となっております！
and it's a song filled with Koyori-ness!
さらにですね、こちら...えー、このあと6月16日の24時...
Furthermore, it will be released... um, at midnight on June 16th...
6月17日の0時、0時になった瞬間にですね、販売リリースされます！
so as soon as it becomes June 17th, it will be available for purchase and streaming!
すげー！みんな、あの「3Dおめでとう」の気持ちで、お安いんでね、
Awesome! Everyone, please buy it as a "3D congratulations" gift. It's cheap!
1曲、1曲だけなんでお安いんで、絶対買ってください！よろしくお願いします！
It's just one song, so it's not expensive. Please buy it! Thank you!
さらに！今多分オープンしたと思うんですけども、「WAO!!」のMV、
And! I think it's probably live now, but the MV for "WAO!!"...
このお披露目配信が終わったあと、21時5分ぐらいからかな、プレミア公開を行います！
will have a premiere after this debut stream ends, probably around 9:05 PM!
是非とも、MVも是非見てってください！
Please, please go and watch the MV too!
超可愛く仕上げてありますので、
It's been made to look super cute,
MVも見てね！お願いします！
so please watch the MV! I'm counting on you!
そして、
And also,
ここで歌って踊っちゃいます！シャキーン！
I'm going to sing and dance right here! Shaking!
『WAO!!』をね、みんなにお届けするのは、
Delivering "WAO!!" to everyone,
やっぱりこのお披露目の場で初めてお届けしたいなと思ったので、
I really wanted to do it for the first time at this debut,
DECO*27さんがね、一生懸命もう、こよりをいっぱい詰めてくださった、
DECO*27 worked hard and filled it with so much of Koyori,
めっちゃ可愛くてかっこいい曲なので、
it's a super cute and cool song,
ここで踊りもめっちゃね、頑張って、これ一番頑張ってるくらい頑張ってるので、
I worked really hard on the dancing here too, maybe harder than anything else,
是非最後まで見て聞いていってくれたら嬉しいです！
so I'd be happy if you watched and listened until the end!
それでは本日最後の曲、
Well then, the final song for today,
博衣こより初めてのオリジナル曲、
Hakui Koyori's very first original song,
聴いてください、『WAO!!』！
please listen to "WAO!!"!
もう君の心チクっとしちゃえ
I'll prick your heart
わおーん！
Wao-n!
絶対無理、思っちゃうし
I think "definitely impossible"
だってだって不安になるし
Because, because I get anxious
全然嘘つけないし
I can't lie at all
だってだってバカ正直だし
Because, because I'm foolishly honest
目指すキラキラもきっと僕次第
The sparkle I aim for is surely up to me
ビター？ギブアップなんて言わないんだから
Bitter? I won't say "I give up"
じっとしてらんないし
I can't stay still
だってだって動いちゃうし
Because, because I keep moving
1, 1, ステップアップ
1, 1, Step up
ちっとずつ進めば夢の式解けちゃうの
If I advance bit by bit, I can solve the formula of dreams
なりたい僕を 君が好きを僕を
The "me" I want to be, the "me" you like
ちゃんと余りなく見せたいの
I want to show you honestly
あっチャチャ びっくりするほどできないじゃん
Acha-cha, I'm surprisingly unable to do it
間違って悩んだりばっかりじゃん
I'm just making mistakes and worrying
けど君に見つけて欲しくて
But I want you to find me
僕も君を迎えに行くんだ 出会えたならハッピー
I'm coming to meet you too, I'll be happy if we meet
わーおわーお叫んじゃえ
Wao, wao, let's shout
泣いて喘いで愛して 尻尾振って
Crying, gasping, loving, wagging my tail
わーおわーお叫んじゃえ
Wao, wao, let's shout
だめな僕をどうか覚えておいて
Please remember the useless me
もう君の心チクっとしちゃえ
I'll prick your heart
もうどうしようとか たまに思っちゃって沈んだり
Sometimes I think "what should I do" and feel down
案外いけるかも ふわり浮かんじゃっても元通り
Maybe I can do it, even if I float up lightly, I'm back to normal
ベッタリがやめられない
I can't stop being clingy
おすわりってそれなんだっけ？
What was "sit" again?
うっかりが止められない
I can't stop being careless
また歩いて棒に当たるの
I'll walk and hit a pole again
1, 1, ステップアップ
1, 1, Step up
死んだふりしてるのやめて
Stop pretending to be dead
はい！こっちおいで
Yes! Come over here
欲しがる君と あげすぎな僕とで
With you wanting and me giving too much
もっといける気がしています
I feel like we can go further
あっチャチャ びっくりするほどできないじゃん
Acha-cha, I'm surprisingly unable to do it
間違って悩んだりばっかりじゃん
I'm just making mistakes and worrying
けど君に見つけて欲しくて
But I want you to find me
僕も君を迎えに行くんだ 出会えたならハッピー
I'm coming to meet you too, I'll be happy if we meet
だって やっぱりひとりじゃだめだけど
Because after all, I'm no good alone
集まってバカしてわおっちゃえば
If we gather, act foolish, and wao together
ほら いつでも言える「おかえり」
Look, I can say "welcome back" anytime
僕君に伝えたいんだ 大いなるハッピー
I want to tell you, a great happiness
わーおわーお叫んじゃえ
Wao, wao, let's shout
泣いて喘いで愛して 尻尾振って
Crying, gasping, loving, wagging my tail
わーおわーお叫んじゃえ
Wao, wao, let's shout
だめな僕をどうか覚えておいて
Please remember the useless me
目指すキラキラもきっと僕次第！
The sparkle I aim for is surely up to me!
ビター？ギブアップなんて言わないんだ
Bitter? I won't say "I give up"
加速メラメラぶっちぎり次第で
With accelerating passion, depending on how I break through
あぐれずに希望へと大暴走
Without stopping, a great rampage towards hope
君の心チクっとしちゃって
I'll prick your heart
いいじゃん ハッピージャン！
It's fine, it's happy!
はーい！ということで、『WAO!!』どうだったかな？最高だったでしょ！
Haa-i! So, how was "WAO!!"? It was the best, right!
あっつーい！
It's hot!
ということでこの後ですね、えー『WAO!!』のMV、すぐ21時5分から、
So after this, uh, the MV for "WAO!!" will have its premiere
発表、あ、プレミア公開させていただきますのでそれも見ていってください！
starting soon at 21:05, so please go and watch that too!
そして、24時になったら公開されます、リリースされますので、
And at 24:00, it will be released [on streaming services],
それもぜひぜひおめでとうの気持ちで手に取ってください！
so please get it with a celebratory feeling!
『WAO!!』、いっぱい歌ってね！よろしく！
Please sing "WAO!!" a lot! Thanks!
そして、3Dお披露目配信1時間お供に見てくれてありがとう！
And thank you for sticking with me for an hour for the 3D debut stream!
これから3Dになって、できることいっぱい増えて、いろんなことやっていきたいと思ってるので、
Now that I have a 3D model, the things I can do have increased, and I want to try various things,
応援これからもよろしくな！
so please continue to support me!
助手くん、みんな、大好きだぞ！ありがとう！
Joshu-kun, everyone, I love you all! Thank you!
こよの3Dお披露目を見にきてくれて、
こよに出逢ってくれて、いつも
応援してくれて、本当にありがとう！
ここからまた1歩スタート！？
たくさんの「楽しい」を一緒に
過ごしていけるように、
より一層がんばります！
助手くん、大好きだ〜〜〜！！
2022.6.16 博衣こより
Thank you so much for watching Koyo's 3D debut,
for meeting Koyo, and for always supporting me!
Starting another step from here!?
So that we can spend many "fun" times together,
I'll work even harder!
Joshu-kun, I love you~~~!!
2022.6.16 Hakui Koyori